paisawapas.com 2019-03-15

# Privacy Policy | Paisawapas.com

We at Paisawapas.com understand the value of your privacy and make every possible effort to ensure that all your personal information remains secure with us.

This Privacy Policy dictates what information we may collect about you, how we may use it, the choices you have concerning its use and whether we share it with any third party. For any queries or concerns regarding this policy, you may contact us.

**An Overview**

Paisawapas.com stores, processes and uses your personal details in order to provide you cashback, customer support and various other services.

In this document, "We" and "us" refers to Paisawapas.com. "Retailers" refer to online merchants, stores and businesses affiliated with us.

**Information we collect**

**Personal Information**

When you signup with Paisawapas.com, we collect your name, gender and email address. We also capture your IP address for security purposes. Your email address is critical for a seamless communication between you and Paisawapas.com.

Then providing rest of your personal details is optional for you. These details include date of birth, age, phone number and personal interests.

Your personal information helps us to know your better enabling us to serve you better too.

**Sensitive Details**

In order to process your request for a wire transfer, we collect your bank account details such as bank account number and the IFSC code of your bank branch. We also collect and store your mailing address in case you opt for cheque to redeem your cashback.

**Site Usage Details**

We also keep a log of your movement on Paisawapas.com. These details contribute to our research and analysis and help us to enhance our layout, design and user interface. In order, to keep your cashback balance updated, we also keep a track of your clicks to retailer pages. We do not store the details such as your bank account number, credit/debit card number or any other information that you might provide while making a purchase on any of our affiliated retailer's website. It may also be possible we may want to use your personal information for special means or purpose, not stated in our privacy policy. In this case, we will seek your prior consent before using your personal details.

**Information Sharing**

We do not share any of your personal details with any third party unless you may specifically give us your consent to do so. However, we may share your details with retailers in order to validate or track your cashback earnings. We may also need to share your information with organizations that assist us in our various business processes.

We may also be bound to share your information if we are forced to do so by the law, or receive a valid request by a law enforcement or government authority.

In the event of a merger, acquisition, sale or any other kind of ownership transfer of Paisawapas.com, you would be duly notified about the change of ownership status or use of your personal information.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of data which enclose information sent from a website and are stored by the user's browser on the hard drive. This information is protected as it cannot be accessed by any other website.

**Cookie Usage :**

Cookies enable us to track your purchases on retailer's website and calculate your cashback amounts. Cookies provide us details such as the retailer on which you have shopped on, the exact timing of the purchase and other relevant details.

Cookies also help us to keep a record of your preferences, so we can present you offers best suited to your needs.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is one of our prime concerns. We employ the most rigorous measures to ensure that your personal information remains secure and protected at all times. All information you provide is stored on secure servers with restricted internal access. However, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your information as complete security of information during transmission is virtually impossible.

If you happen to have any concern or query regarding our security measures, you may feel free to contact our support centre.

**Updating Account Information and Mailing Settings**

Once you become a part of the Paisawapas.com family, we give you periodic updates about new offers, coupons and other services of your interest. However, we understand that lot of emails can be a nuisance, so we give you the option of limiting our communications with you as per your needs. Some communications that are critical to the cashback service can never be opted out. We never send you junk emails or spam.

All of your account information can be updated or modified form your account panel except for your name and email address.

**Company Details**

For any queries regarding our privacy policy you may contact us through our email id contact@paisawapas.com.
